>> Greg: ARE YOU OKAY?
MORE BAD HOMBRES ARE ABOUT TO
GET BARBECUED, TURNING UP THE
HEAT ON VENEZUELA AS HE WANTS TO
BOMB THE EVER LIVING OUT OF
NARCO TERRORISTS IN THE
CARIBBEAN KILLING MORE THAN 20
PEOPLE.
REPORTING ON U.S. OPS
HELICOPTERS OPERATING WITHIN
90 MILES OF THE VENEZUELAN
COAST.
47 CONFIRMING HE HAS AUTHORIZED
THE CIA TO TAKE ACTION WITHIN
THE COUNTRY.
>> I DON'T WANT TO TELL YOU
EXACTLY, BUT WE ARE LOOKING AT
LAND NOW, BECAUSE WE HAVE THE
SEA UNDER CONTROL.
WE HAVE HAD A COUPLE OF DAYS
WHERE THERE IS NOT A VOTE TO BE
FOUND.
AND I DO THAT IS A GOOD THING,
NOT A BAD THING.
>> WOULD YOU TAKE OUT --
>> IT'S A RIDICULOUS QUESTION TO
BE GIVEN.
IT WOULD BE A RIDICULOUS
QUESTION ANSWER, I THINK THEY
ARE FEELING HEAT.
>> Greg: IT'S A RIDICULOUS
QUESTION FOR ME TO ANSWER, BUT
IT'S NOT A RIDICULOUS QUESTION,
OKAY, WE HAVE TO DO A LITTLE
VICTORY LAP, BECAUSE YOU WERE
HERE FOR FIVE YEARS AGO WHEN WE
POSITED TAKING OUT FENTON ALL
LABS IN MEXICO, AND PEOPLE WERE
SAYING, OH, MY GOD, YOU CAN'T DO
THAT, IT'S UNCONSTITUTIONAL.
YOU THINK YOU WANT ONE BETTER?
>> Dana: ONE THING --
THIS NEWS JUST CAME OUT THAT THE
ADMIRAL OVERSEEN THE ATTACKS
AGAINST FOLKS IN THE CARIBBEAN
IS STEPPING DOWN AND DON'T HAVE
A LOT OF INFORMATION YET, THERE
IS A "NEW YORK TIMES" PIECE
WHERE THEY ARE STEPPING DOWN, SO
STEPPING DOWN AS THIS IS HEATING
UP, MAYBE HE DISAGREED OR MAYBE
HE --
THEY DID NOT THINK HE WAS THE
RIGHT PERSON FOR THE SECRETARY
OF WAR HAS THANKED HIM FOR HIS
SERVICE.
>> Greg: IS HE OVERWEIGHT?
>> Dana: HE DOES NOT LOOK AT,
BUT IN A WAY I THINK HE WANTS
THIS FIGHT, BECAUSE THEN IT
ALLOWS HIM TO SAY TO HIS PEOPLE,
OH, LOOK, THE YANKEE
IMPERIALISTS ARE COMING AFTER
ME.
HE IS THE WORST LEADER, HE IS
THE WORST AND HE ALLOWS ALL OF
THIS TERRORISM TO HAPPEN BECAUSE
THERE IS NO OTHER WAY FOR HIM TO
FUND THE COUNTRY.
AND THOUGH A WOMAN WHO WON THE
NOBEL PRIZE LAST WEEK WAS A
OPPOSITION LEADER WHO WAS TRYING
TO DO GOOD THINGS FOR THAT
COUNTRY.
SO I DON'T EXACTLY KNOW WHERE
THIS GOES, IT'S INTERESTING IN
TERMS OF MILITARY LAW IS THIS
ALLOWED, IS IT NOT?
YOU HAVE SOME REPUBLICANS IN
CONGRESS SAYING ARE WE GOING TO
GET A SAY IN THIS?
BUT WHAT PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS IS
THE AUTHORITY TO BE ABLE TO SAY
I NEED TO PROTECT MY COUNTRY
FROM TERRORISTS, AND HE HAS
DEEMED THEM AS TERRORISTS, AND
SO THEREFORE IT SEEMS TO ME HE
HAS THE AUTHORITY TO DO IT.
>> Greg: JESSE, I WILL ASK YOU
A DIFFICULT AND CHALLENGING
QUESTION, DO YOU BELIEVE NARCO
TERRORISTS HAVE RIGHTS?
>> Jesse: ON THE HIGH SEAS?
IF A LAWYER SAYS NO, I'M FOR IT,
LET'S GO GET THEM.
THIS IS ABOUT REGIME CHANGE AND
VENEZUELA.
WE HAD 10% OF THE NAVAL POWER IN
THE REGION.
WE HAD THE DESTROYER FLEET,
F-35'S THERE, AND I WE HAVE
HELICOPTERS WHICH ARE USED FOR
THE SPECIAL FORCES.
SO THIS IS SERIOUS STUFF, THE
CIA HAS BEEN UNLEASHED WITH A
$50 BILLION BOUNTY ON THIS GUY'S
HEAD, DONALD TRUMP IS
CONSIDERING STRIKES ON
VENEZUELAN SOIL.
SO WE ARE ENGAGED IN WHAT WE
LIKE TO CALL SOME FRIENDLY
GUNBOAT DIPLOMACY AND
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" REPORTED
THAT WE HAVE BEEN IN
NEGOTIATIONS WITH THE REGIME AND
THE REGIME SAID WE WILL GIVE YOU
DOMINANT STEAKS AND OUR OILS,
ARTICLES, AND OUR MINERAL
WEALTH, AND WE HAVE AGREED TO
CUT TIES WITH CHINA AND RUSSIA
AND THEY SAID NO.
SO THAT TELLS ME THERE IS GOING
TO BE MAJOR ACTION AGAINST
MADURO PRETTY SOON.
AND THESE THINGS IN
LATIN AMERICA COULD GO SIDEWAYS,
BUT ALSO THEY COULD BE LAYUPS.
AND IF IT IS A LAYUP AND THEY
ARE DEPOSED, WE ARE BASICALLY
MONRO DOCTORING, WE CALL IT THE
DUNN ROAD DOCTORING OUT OF
LATIN AMERICA OF CHINA AND
RUSSIA.
AND WHAT DOES THAT DEAL?
AFTER THE SUCCESSFUL STRIKES
AGAINST THE IRANIAN REGIME, THAT
BASICALLY TAKES THIS BIG PILE OF
DETERRENCE AND SHOVES IT RIGHT
AND TAIWAN'S FACE, RIGHT IN
UKRAINE'S FACE AND DONALD TRUMP
IS YIELDING A LOT OF POWER
INTERNATIONALLY.
>> Greg: IS THIS JUST ANOTHER
EXAMPLE OF TOXIC MASCULINITY NOW
BEING EXPORTED BEYOND OUR
BORDERS?
>> Jessica: I'M SURE THE GROUP
CHAT IS CRAZY WHEN THE GUYS IN
CHARGE OF THIS, HOPEFULLY NOT ON
SIGNAL ANYMORE.
I REMEMBER THE DAY THE FIRST
VOTE WAS STRUCK, AND JESSE TOLD
ME, DO YOU WANT TO BE ON THE
SIDE OF NARCO TERRORISTS?
AND I SAID NO, NOT ESPECIALLY,
LET'S SEE WHERE THIS GOES AND
NOW WE ARE UP TO MULTIPLE BOATS,
IT'S NOT JUST VENEZUELAN,
COLOMBIAN BOATS SAY ONE WAS
THEIRS, AND TWO ARE NATIONALISTS
WERE MURDERED WHEN THEY WERE
STRUCK, AND THAT THEY WEREN'T
TWO DRUG TRAFFICKERS.
NOW, DO I KNOW IF THAT'S THE
CASE OR NOT?
I'M NOT SURE, BUT THERE IS A
REASON --
>> Greg: DON'T LET THAT STOP
YOU.
>> Jessica: DON'T LET THE
CONSTITUTION STOP YOU.
WHERE THEY ARE SUPPOSED TO BE
OVERSIGHT AS DANA MENTIONED,
THERE IS DEMOCRATS AND
REPUBLICANS ALIKE SAYING THIS IS
TURNING INTO A HABIT MORE THAN
STRIKING JUST ONE BOATS AND THAT
WE ARE SUPPOSED TO HAVE A SAY IN
THIS.
AND HISTORICALLY SPEAKING, I
KNOW YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE FUN OF
ME, BUT THAT'S WHY I COME TO
WORK EVERY DAY.
DRUG TRAFFICKERS WERE CONSIDERED
CRIMINALS WITH THE DUE PROCESS
RIGHTS, AND THIS IS A
CONVERSATION WE HAVE BEEN HAVING
AS WELL ABOUT UNDOCUMENTED
PEOPLE IN THIS COUNTRY WHO ALSO
HAVE DUE PROCESS RIGHTS AS WAS
AFFIRMED.
AND I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S A GOOD
PRESIDENT OR ROAD TO BE GOING
DOWN THAT HE IS ESSENTIALLY
STARTING SOME DEGREE OF WAR
WITHOUT CONGRESS BEING ABLE TO
SEE ANYTHING.
THE INTEL COMMUNITY, THE PEOPLE
WHO SHARE THESE COMMITTEES ARE
NOT GETTING ANYTHING TO SEE WHAT
IT IS THAT THE BASIS FOR THE
ACTIONS THEY ARE TAKING AND I
DON'T THINK THAT YOU ARE GOING
TO BE THAT COMFORTABLE WITH THE
IDEA OF THEM GOING INTO
VENEZUELAN LAND WITHOUT THERE
BEING ANY VERIFICATION BESIDES,
TRUMP AND PETE HEGSETH SAID SO.
>> Greg: WE WILL HAVE TO WAIT
AND SEE ON THAT.
>> Greg: CHECK YOUR TEXTS.
>> Greg: HI, EMILY.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
I WANTED TO ASK YOU ABOUT THE
175,000 AMERICANS APPLYING FOR
JOBS.
BUT I WAS NOT SURE IF YOU WANTED
TO TALK ABOUT THAT OR THIS.
>> Jessica: YOU DON'T CARE
WHAT SHE WANTS, YOU FORCE
WHATEVER TOPIC YOU WANT DOWN MY
THROAT.
>> Greg: THAT IS TRUE.
>> Emily: FIRST OF ALL, I HAVE
RESPONDED TO THIS.
THE PRESIDENT CAN OBVIOUSLY
DIRECT COVERT CIA OPERATIONS
UNDER THE NATIONAL SECURITY ACT
OF 1947 WITH PRESIDENTIAL
FINDING WHICH BASICALLY IS A
CLASSIFIED BRIEFING TO THE GANG
OF EIGHT, AND NOTIFYING
CONGRESS, AND THEY AUTHORIZE THE
FUNDING THROUGH THE HOUSE OF THE
SENATE OF APPROPRIATIONS
COMMITTEE'S OWN INTELLIGENCE AND
THE POINT IS THAT IF THEY WANTED
TO WITHDRAW FUNDING, GO AHEAD.
THERE'S NO OPACITY INVOLVED.
AND THE THIRD OPTION IS FOR THE
SANCTITY AND SECURITY OF OUR
EXECUTIVE BRANCH IN ADDITION TO
AMERICANS.
AND I THINK IT'S INTERESTING
THAT THIS MIGHT DESTABILIZE
VENEZUELA, BECAUSE TO ME THE
OSTRICH HEAD IN THE SAND THAT WE
SUFFERED FROM UNDER THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION AND THE BIDEN
ADMINISTRATION, TO ONLY EMBOLDEN
TERRORISTS.
I DON'T ARGUE THAT WE CAN PUT
THEM IN THE CRIMINAL DRUG
RUNNING BOX VERY NEATLY, BECAUSE
THEY HAVE PIVOTED SIGNIFICANTLY
SINCE PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS TAKEN
OFFICE AND HOW THEY ARE INTO A
WHOLE HOST OF ILLICIT INDUSTRIES
PUTTING OVER THROUGH CANADA AND
TAKING ADVANTAGE OF THEIR
LOOPHOLES THERE, THEIR READING
AVOCADO FARMS.
>> Greg: NOT AVOCADOS.
>> Emily: LIQUID GOLD.
AND THE WHOLE POINT IS IF YOU
THINK FOR ONE SECOND THEY ARE
GOING TO LET $1 OF THEIR
BILLIONS UPON BILLIONS OF INCOME
GAINED ILLICITLY EVERY YEAR TO
BE DIVERTED OR EXTINGUISHED IN
ANY WAY, THEY WILL FIGHT TO THE
DEATH, BUT I AT LEAST HAVE FAITH
IN OUR ADMINISTRATION THAT WE
AREN'T GOING TO TAKE IT LYING
DOWN, AND THAT 175.
HERE'S WHAT I LOVE.
YOU REMEMBER WHEN THEY PUT THE
CHOOSE YOUR FIGHTER AND BLESS
THEM FOR TRYING, BUT OLD PEOPLE
HOPPING AROUND AND SOMEONE IS
DOING A TIKTOK VIDEO.
AND HERE THEY ACTUALLY HAVE, THE
DEPARTMENT OF HOMELAND SECURITY
THAT SAYS CHOOSE YOUR MISSION
AND WHEN IT TALKS ABOUT THE
BRAVE MEN AND WOMEN THAT ARE
SIGNING UP IN RECORD NUMBERS NOW
TO DEFEND AND SUPPORT THIS
NATION.
IF YOU WANT TO BE AN ATTORNEY
FOR THE CLOSERS, FOR THE
RESOLUTE, FOR THOSE THAT
REPRESENT THE USA, FOR THOSE
THAT ARE OFFICERS, FOR THE
ENFORCERS, FOR THE BRAVE, FOR
THOSE THAT FIGHT TO KEEP AMERICA
SAFE IN DIRECT CONTRAST TO THE
NAMES THAT THE DEMOCRAT
LEADERSHIP AND ELECTED OFFICIALS
AS CONGRESSMEN AND SENATORS
CALLED THEM, AND FASCISTS, THESE
ARE THE BRAVE.
THEY ARE